{
    "subject": "resource/United_States_Senate_election_in_Kansas,_2014",
    "predicate": "ontology/startDate",
    "object": "2014-11-04",
    "human_readable": "The start date of the United States Senate election in Kansas in 2014 is November 4, 2014.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9799686670303345,
            "question": "What date did the Kansas Senate election begin in 2014?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9640327095985413,
            "question": "When was the United States Senate election in Kansas held in 2014?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9456903338432312,
            "question": "What type of election took place in Kansas on November 4th, 2014?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9424832463264465,
            "question": "On what date did the United States Senate election begin in Kansas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8870318531990051,
            "question": "What state had a Senate election on November 4th, 2014?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8761900067329407,
            "question": "November 4th, 2014 is significant for what event in Kansas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7928662896156311,
            "question": "What month and day did the Kansas Senate election begin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7519984841346741,
            "question": "In which year was the Kansas Senate election held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7509986758232117,
            "question": "Which political office was up for election in Kansas in 2014?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7379404902458191,
            "question": "For which political body was the election held in Kansas in 2014?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The start date of the United States Senate election in Kansas in 2014 is November 4, 2014.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6212_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which political office was up for election in Kansas in 2014?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6212_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which year was the Kansas Senate election held?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6212_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What month and day did the Kansas Senate election begin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6212_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_120.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6212_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the provided context information, the overview for the \"1992 United States Senate election in Kansas\" and multiple other elections including \"The 2014 United States Senate election in Kansas\" mention dates on which these elections took place. Specifically, it states that \"The 2014 United States Senate election in Kansas was held on November 4, 2014.\" Therefore, the statement about the start date of the United States Senate election in Kansas in 2014 being November 4, 2014, is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}